Uh, how about, uh,
you keep the store open late...
...and we throw a party for people
who don't have dates?
That actually sounds kind of nice.
(Raj:)The theme will be that the greatest love
a man can have is love he has with himself.
(Stuart:)That's good...
(Stuart:)...or maybe something
a little less hand-in-the-pants.
Oh. Alex, excellent.
(Sheldon:)I have a research problem
that I believe you can help with.
(Alex:)Oh, Dr. Cooper, thank you.
(Alex:)I've been waiting for an opportunity
to contribute to your scientific work.
Oh, no, that's not gonna happen. No.
(Sheldon:)What I need you to do is find
a Valentine's gift for my girlfriend.
(Alex:)I passed up an opportunity to work at
Fermilab to take this job with you.
(Sheldon:)Well, I guess those chaps will have to have
someone else buy their girlfriends presents.
Now, here is... Oh, let's see...
This is...